export  const questions = [
    {
        question:'What do we call the Angels who write down what we do ?',
        options:['Israfil','Kiraman Katibin','Mikail', 'Izrail'],
        answer:'Kiraman Katibin'
    },
    {
        question:'The Muslims started fasting in the month of Ramadan,in what year?',
        options:['2 years after hijra','On Prophet burial','From beginning of the world','3rd year after hijra'],
        answer:'3rd year after hijra'
    },
     {
       question:'THE SMOKE is a surah in the QURAN termed ____ in arabic',
       options:['Surah-Rum','Surah-Qalam','Surah-Layl','Surah-Dukhan'],
       answer:'Surah-Dukhan'
     },
    {
        question:'The Holy QURAN was revealed in the period of _____ ?',
        options:['20years','23years','9months','63years'],
        answer:'23years'
    },
    {
        question:'The first kid to accept Islam is ____?',
        options:['Uthman ibn Affan','Prophet Shuaib','Ali ibn Abi Talib','Abubakar ibn Quhaffah'],
        answer:'Ali ibn Abi Talib'
    },
    {
        question:' Pillars of Islam are also called ...…',
        options:['Qadr ul Islam','Arkanal Islam','Yusuf Islam','Fi Amanillah'],
        answer:'Arkanal Islam'
    },
    {
        question:' A prophet is called .......... in Arabic.',
        options:['Nabi','Rasul','Wahi', 'None of the above'],
        answer:'Nabi'
    },
    {
        question:'What does Islam mean ?',
        options:['Islam means to obey Allah (S.W.T.) and follow His commands','Islam means to obey our parents','Islam means to obey our teachers and elders', 'None of the above'],
        answer:'Islam means to obey Allah (s.w.t.) and follow His commands'
    },
    {
        question:'Islam has how many pillars ?',
        options:['8 pillars','5 pillars','3 pillars','10 pillars'],
        answer:'5 pillars'
  
    },
    {
        question:'Allah (s.w.t.) has ......…',
        options:['A son','A partner','No partner','A daughter'],
        answer:'No partner'
    },
]
